<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on LPWANSys</title>
    <link>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/lpwansys/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on LPWANSys</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ntusg-iot.github.io/lpwansys/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LPWANSys</title>
      <link>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/lpwansys/home/lpwansys/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/lpwansys/home/lpwansys/</guid>
      <description>The 1st Workshop on LPWAN Systems and Applications in Conjunction with IEEE ICPADS 2018
December 11-13, 2018, Sentosa, Singapore</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CFP</title>
      <link>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/lpwansys/home/cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/lpwansys/home/cfp/</guid>
      <description>The emerging low-power wide-area network (LPWAN) technologies will largely increase the degree of connectivity of Internet of Things (IoT) and enable the deep penetration of smart objects into the territories that challenged the existing short-range wireless technologies, such as urban areas with dense buildings, underground structures, uninstrumented rural and wild areas, etc. With the increasingly available LPWAN platforms (e.g., LoRaWAN and NBIoT) and the relevant development tools, research shall explore the challenges, issues, and opportunities in the improvement and deployment of LPWANs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Important Dates</title>
      <link>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/lpwansys/home/dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/lpwansys/home/dates/</guid>
      <description> Paper Submission Deadline: September 15, 2018 Paper Notification: September 26, 2018 Camera Ready: October 1, 2018  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop Organizers</title>
      <link>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/lpwansys/home/organizers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/lpwansys/home/organizers/</guid>
      <description> Program Chairs  Rui Tan, Nanyang Technological University Jiliang Wang, Tsinghua University Jun Huang, Peking University  Program Committee TBD
Web Chair  Chaojie Gu, Nanyang Technological University  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submission Guideline</title>
      <link>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/lpwansys/home/guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/lpwansys/home/guide/</guid>
      <description>Each submission must not exceed 6 pages in the IEEE 8.5 &amp;ldquo;x11&amp;rdquo; two-column format with 10-point font, including tables, figures, and references. Submissions should be formatted using the template provided below and in PDF format. The review process is single-blind so the submissions should include author information.
All submissions will be reviewed by the Program Committee members. At least one author of the accepted paper should register the workshop and present the paper in the workshop in order for the accepted paper to be included into the IEEE digital library.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>